<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scikit-learn on Jameson Thai</title>
    <link>https://jamesonthai.github.io/tags/scikit-learn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scikit-learn on Jameson Thai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jamesonthai.github.io/tags/scikit-learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer</title>
      <link>https://jamesonthai.github.io/publications/usc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamesonthai.github.io/publications/usc/</guid>
      <description>  Develop web application to enable users to analyze different quality metrics of software systems as it evolves over time. Visualize and construct a Tensorflow.js predictive model for predicting when, how, and to what extent developers influence software quality attributes. Introduce new features in frontend to visualize data as well as conduct real-time machine learning techniques on presented data.  Research Paper Links  Towards Better Understanding of Software Maintainability Evolution Towards Better Understanding of Software Quality Evolution through Commit-Impact Analysis A scalable and efficient approach for compiling and analyzing commit history  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Reviews - Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jamesonthai.github.io/projects/creations/amazon-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamesonthai.github.io/projects/creations/amazon-review/</guid>
      <description>I led two fellow students to develop a Python recomendation system for suggesting ratings for a user&amp;rsquo;s review through collabortive filters and machine learning algorithms achieving our highest accuracy of 89%.
Goals Acquire Amazon Dataset Exploratory analysis of dataset Use ML Algorithms to predict review ratings Build Jupyter notebook to predict ratings Visualize preprocessed information and compiled Bag Of Words Present findings to general and informed audience  Algorithms  KNN Naive Bayes Ordered Logistic Regression Linear SVM Doc2Vec Decision Trees  Dataset We filtered the initial dataset of over 12 million reviews (12 GB) into five separate data frames corresponding to their star ratings using Pandas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Intern</title>
      <link>https://jamesonthai.github.io/publications/wb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamesonthai.github.io/publications/wb/</guid>
      <description> Developed Python image identification pipeline and model for identifying DC Universe characters in a given DCU comic page. Built Xception Convolutional Neural Network in Keras framework while training model on AWS EC2 instance. Present project architecture and convolutional neural network model&amp;rsquo;s layer activation to WB executive, data intelligence team, and DCU stakeholders.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>