<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JSON on Jameson Thai</title>
    <link>https://jamesonthai.github.io/tags/json/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JSON on Jameson Thai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 12:41:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jamesonthai.github.io/tags/json/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Riot Champion Trend and Item Recommender</title>
      <link>https://jamesonthai.github.io/projects/creations/riot-games-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamesonthai.github.io/projects/creations/riot-games-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Riot Champion Trends and Item Recommender &amp;ldquo;is a data science project that aims to visualize a user&amp;rsquo;s performance by comparing their matches and timeline data against professional or similar ranking players using R and Plotly.&amp;rdquo; Based on this information, if there is enough correlation between player performance and items to wins, then recommend corresponding items based on matchups.
Goals Primary
Compile list of professional players from Season 9 of League of Legends Acquire Data from RIOT Servers Build Pipeline for automated collection Conduct data analysis and visualize results &amp;ndash; In Progress Determine if secondary objectives are viable  Secondary</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Reviews - Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jamesonthai.github.io/projects/creations/amazon-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamesonthai.github.io/projects/creations/amazon-review/</guid>
      <description>Leading two fellow students to develop a Python recomendation system for suggesting ratings for a user&amp;rsquo;s review through collabortive filters and machine learning algorithms achieving our highest accuracy of 89%. This is a multi-classification
Goals Acquire Amazon Dataset Exploratory analysis of dataset Use ML Algorithms to predict review ratings Build Jupyter notebook to predict ratings Visualize preprocessed information and compiled Bag Of Words Present findings to general and informed audience  Algorithms  KNN Naive Bayes Ordered Logistic Regression Linear SVM Doc2Vec Decision Trees  Dataset We filtered the initial dataset of over 12 million reviews (12 GB) into five separate csv corresponding to their star ratings using Pandas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How In The World</title>
      <link>https://jamesonthai.github.io/projects/creations/how-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jamesonthai.github.io/projects/creations/how-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Mobile game designed for children ages five to nine in an effort to teach youths about cultural literacy while being imformative but also fun. Leading a team of five, we were introduced to the agile methodology as we worked with our client. To develop this came we taught ourselves Lua and Corona SDK over the course of the semester. The game is live and on the itunes app store!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>